Game: Dai Gyakuten Saiban: Naruhodō Ryūnosuke no Bōken
Developer: Capcom

Ripper: WTails358 (I usually go by WarioTails358)

Notes:The models have the outline effect as part of their model, its not a shader or anything in the game. 
To use it, you need to set the outline models to backface cull in the 3d modeling program you use.
I included a "outline texture" for the outline models since they didnt come with one. you can tell
what meshes are the outlines as when dragging a texture on to them they will mostly be a single color, try to group them together
so its easier to know what is what. 

No credit is needed.

